<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Sidharth Arya</title>
        <link>https://sidhartharya.github.io/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Sidharth Arya</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>sidhartharya10@gmail.com (Sidharth Arya)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>sidhartharya10@gmail.com (Sidharth Arya)</webMaster><copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sidhartharya.github.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>A quicker way to reach localhost with qutebrowser</title>
    <link>https://sidhartharya.github.io/a-quicker-way-to-reach-localhost-with-qutebrowser/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0530</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://sidhartharya.github.io/a-quicker-way-to-reach-localhost-with-qutebrowser/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Qutebrowser Qutebrowser is the best web browser for developers, hands down. Nothing can compare to the flexibility it offers. Now, ofcourse other web browser must have ways of enabling and disabling various fancy features, but it&rsquo;s much harder to achieve.
I have a number of scripts that i use on a daily basis in qutebrowser which i maintain here (dotfiles/Browser/Qutebrowser/userscripts at master · SidharthArya/dotfiles ) on a daily basis.
The Problem One of the issues i have sometimes is to reach localhost on various ports quickly.]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Running ipython inside a python script</title>
    <link>https://sidhartharya.github.io/running-ipython-inside-a-python-script/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0530</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://sidhartharya.github.io/running-ipython-inside-a-python-script/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Imagine you are writing a very convoluted program with all sorts of threading magic. You want to continuously test various sections of your program before moving on with the next task. Would you rather write all the functions in the file at the same time and start debugging the code for errors, or would you rather fire up an ipython shell with your program loaded up and available to you?]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>What is this blog about</title>
    <link>https://sidhartharya.github.io/what-is-this-blog-about/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jun 2021 00:00:00 &#43;0530</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://sidhartharya.github.io/what-is-this-blog-about/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[To blog - To share, To connect, To create, To inspire
To be honest, i wanted to start my blog in an incredibly attractive way, and so i searched a quote. And&hellip;. here we are. A quote i found on google, that makes it seem like my blog has a lot of purpose behind it. But, how exactly do you make an introduction attractive enough for you to gain enough ad revenue is all i am thinking right now.]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
